<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BetLiveScore</string>
    <string name="bl1">Basketball is a fantastic sport, but do you want to make money from it? Even if you enjoy watching it, there are numerous risks associated with betting on different leagues. We can provide you what you have been seeking for.. Best betting choices from the best 365 BetLiveScore tipsters on a variety of basketball leagues ranging from the NBA to Germany highest level. If you join us, you will not be disappointed.</string>
    <string name="bl2">Baseball is a relatively unknown sport, yet there must be a reason why it is so popular in the United States. Our forecast will assist you in comprehending this ballgame and enjoying every moment of it. Baseball betting is done on a money line, which means you can lay or take money odds. In contrast to point spread bets, the reward on a winning selection is determined by the odds. Baseball odds are given as a three-digit money line. Every money line is based on $100. In baseball betting, the run line is equal to the point spread in other sports betting.</string>
    <string name="bl3">Although American football originated in the United States, it has since spread to Europe and other countries. American football is comparable to rugby, but the regulations are different. It is a team sport played on a rectangular field by two teams of eleven players each. The first game of American football was played on November 6, 1869. American football is one of the most popular and widely watched sports in the United States.</string>
    <string name="bl4">There are numerous more events that do not fall under the category of "sports," yet you are interested in betting on them. Guess Dota 2, League of Legends, CS:GO, and other e-sports games. Bet on e-sports and experience a variety of sensations. There is pre-match and in-play betting available, with odds shown as fractions or decimals. When it comes to betting, you can choose between sports, events, and leagues, just like you can with most other sports. Then simply click on your bets to have them added to your betting slip.</string>
    <string name="bl5">Football is the most popular sport in the world, which is why there are so many bets. Football draws a large number of fans who tune in to witness the most exciting events in Europe, including the UEFA Champions League, the Premier League, and the Spanish La Liga. Predicting football results is difficult, but 365 BetLiveScore tipsters are attempting to help better understand the principles of different leagues and identify the finest betting predictions for each game.</string>
    <string name="bl6">Handball League and essential concerns such as injuries, moods, the significance of the game, and so on. Handball and each player in the sports here are being scrutinized thoroughly based on the match forecast. It is possible to gamble on how much a team will win in handball. Almost always, this will take the shape of an over/under bet. You would win your wager if the number was greater than or less than the amount you chose. For example, Team A should win by more than ten points. Handball is a high-scoring, fast-paced sport. The game is suited for real-time wagering. Handball betting offers a variety of excellent betting options, including two-way and three-way bets. Spread bets and Over/Under bets are two common types.</string>
    <string name="bl7">Ice hockey is a fast-paced sport that is entertaining even if you aren not wagering on it. But does not gambling offer you a rush? NHL, KHL, and other league predictions for all ice hockey lovers. Hockey betting, like most team sports, allows spectators to choose which team they believe will win the game. In addition, gamblers can wager on the overall number of goals scored as well as a variety of alternative betting markets for each game. The money line, puck line, and Over/Under goal total are the most prevalent hockey betting lines.</string>
    <string name="bl8">Other significant events and questions: injuries, moods, the significance of the game, and so on. Other events and every player in the sports here are being thoroughly reviewed, based on the match forecast. The winner of a match is one of the most popular table tennis betting options. Head-to-head betting odds are often offered as money line odds. Bettors must put more money at risk when betting on the favorite. By betting on the underdog, bettors can strive to get a higher return on their investment.</string>
    <string name="bl9">Tennis deserved to be watched by every gambler. Tennis matches take place practically every day of the year. This is a significant benefit to all bettors. Our members like betting on matches of lower caliber as well as ATP or WTA tournaments. A bettor will gain by betting on the underdog if the unfavored player either wins or loses by one game. Betting on the favorite yields a profit only if the favorite wins by at least two games.</string>
    <string name="bl10">Volleyball could be a superb alternative if you want to diversify your top options. This is where you can get information about volleyball matches from across the world. Betting will be as simple as it has never been before with the assistance of other users. The ball is typically played using a person hands or arms, though it is permissible to hit any part of the body. To win a match, teams must first win sets, scoring 25 points more than their opponents. Teams must win by a two-point margin if a set is deadlocked at 24-24. Matches are normally played in best-of-five sets.</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="blt1">Basketball</string>
    <string name="blt2">Baseball</string>
    <string name="blt3">Football</string>
    <string name="blt4">E-Sports</string>
    <string name="blt5">Soccer</string>
    <string name="blt6">Handball</string>
    <string name="blt7">Ice Hockey</string>
    <string name="blt8">Table Tennis</string>
    <string name="blt9">Tennis</string>
    <string name="blt10">Volleyball</string>

  <string name="about2">You can place live bets on any site you want while watching any game you want from any corner of your TV screen in the usual way. As you shall see, such a high level of technical infrastructure necessitates a very large investment budget. This is because, in order for a bookmaker to provide equal high-quality live streaming for all internet connection speeds, he or she must have a very powerful technological infrastructure and a highly specific collection of necessary background.</string>
    <string name="about1">As the name implies, Live Streaming is the transmission of real-time streaming to the end user over the internet and mobile (3G/4G). The availability of such technology, which allows you to access all sports betting events live into your desktop, laptop, or any appropriate mobile communication device, will provide you with a betting opportunity with less danger and much more entertainment.</string>
    <string name="back_button">back_button</string>
    <string name="close_button">close_button</string>
</resources>